Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
The hero's name was Lumiere Silver Million Clover.
He was later hailed as the first Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Devil was sealed for five hundred years, but the day would soon come when the seal would break.
Against all reason in this world, I was transformed into a bird, and I continued to guard Lyk's grimoire.
In the present day, this place is called Hajj Village.
It's situated far away from the royal capital of the Clover Kingdom, a hamlet in the Forsaken Realm.
Asta! Hang in there! I'm sorry. It's all my fault. I'm so sorry.
This? Please, don't worry about it. This is nothing. After all, I'm gonna be the Wizard King, right?
I'm gonna be the Wizard King! I'll keep you and everybody else safe.
The more worrying about food or money, you'll have everything you ever wanted.
I'll prove it. I'll show them all. Show them? Prove what?
That even if you're poor, a commoner and an orphan, you can still become the Wizard King.
You really think so? Yeah. Commoners? Orphans?
Anybody can do it. As long as they're willing to work hard. Anybody? Even me. And even you.
I… I'm never going to cry again. I've decided.
What do you mean? I'll do it too. I'm going to become the Wizard King.
I'll work hard and get strong so I can protect you and everybody else.
I'll do whatever it takes. And I'll never give up!
Good boy.
Again...
Way to get the ball!
Good boy!
So Okey2
Needなく全てを振り払うように
叶えよう約束通り
君は出た世界だ
Let's die in this world
Even how can I drop this world?
All I need is get this strong
We can catch the game
負けないでよ
Biddy and suprasmentでよ
ほら味方に変えて
We can catch the game
失敗しなきゃその通り
その影は見抜いて
We can catch the game
What is this place?
What happened to me?
I thought I was dead
I look like Ligt
What is this?
Have I become him somehow?
Did my spirit implant itself in his body?
That's not it
Judging by how this mana feels
The body I'm in is human
A human that looks like Ligt
I see
So I really did die
What ever Ligt unleashed when our magic was sealed away
It must have been some kind of forbidden spell
And something extremely powerful too
Like reincarnation magic
This light
I can sense them
Every single one
I can feel Raya's soul
And the souls of all the other elves in this village
Ligt must have done this in the final few seconds of his life
And all for the sake of our people
I have been chosen
I'll become Ligt
No matter what it takes
I'll revive all the elves
As for the humans
For going back on their word
For killing the people I loved
They must pay
I swear they will all be annihilated
So these three are the souls
I was able to restore at this juncture
It's as if they never died
But I'll need greater power
To bring back the rest
And that means supplying even more sacrifices
To that end
We will gather the magic stones
That were once kept within our village
But have since been scattered far and wide
And we'll use humans to do it
Smart don't you think
Oh yeah
Agreed
Let's begin
We'll get back at those hateful scum
I'll make sure they suffer endless despair
Indeed
The great rebirth will start with the humans
Resurrecting the elves
Getting revenge on humankind
It was all a misunderstanding
Sadly they had no way of knowing that
Everything that happened was orchestrated by a deceitful devil
Not only the capital
But the entire kingdom was about to be overrun
By darkness
However
At that same time
I saw a glimmer of hope
Is that
A grim war?
My prince
The time has come
The leaves of the clover represent three things
One is integrity
One is hope
And the third one stands for love
Within the fourth leaf dwells good luck
And in the fifth
Lives the devil
But the devil inside the grimoire
Happened to be different from the one who had attacked the elves
This particular being would later be of aid to Asta
The boy with no magic
As for Patry's group
They named themselves the Eye of the Midnight Sun
And searched for the magic stones
By collecting all of these stones
They would be able to resurrect the other elves
Kill them
They ransacked a village
No!
FRECOLION!
Then the capital
Then the underwater temple
Until finally
Every magic stone was theirs
What is that Marie?
It just never ends
I'm so scared
What the hell
Too bad
What is
Your worthless human race is finished
What's happening?
Why do you look?
Klaus talk to me
Don't use such a familiar tone with us
You should know
We aren't teammates or friends
The resurrection was complete
All the elves had returned
Begone humans
At last the time has come for revenge
The one humans
Those who guide the Elves, the Apostles of Sephra.
By infusing Gravitos stones with magic,
we'll open the door below Clover Castle and release the seal on the Underworld.
Huh? What the hell is that?
I don't understand this at all.
This is a magic space that serves as a border between this world and the next,
which the Elves entrusted to the humans through an ancient pact.
It's called the Shadow Palace.
Should they have succeeded in placing the final magic stone into the monument,
the reincarnation spell would have become permanent,
and the souls of the human hosts would be lost forever.
So Asta and the others gathered at the Shadow Palace for the final battle,
but something awaited them.
What is this? A pitch-black magic?
And why is it so cold?
Don't tell me.
Is he...
The devil?
This creature...
What is he?
Though it's still incomplete,
it's been centuries since I've been in my own body,
and it's such a wonderful feeling.
You've used your four-leaf grimoire well, Elf.
I commend you.
I praise you from the bottom of my black heart
for all that you've done up to this moment
and the results you've shown me.
And now, you shall taste the depths of despair,
just as another did all those centuries ago.
Another?
But who?
What is going on here?
That day,
the one who tricked the humans into betraying the elves
was none other than...
Why me, of course!
And then you lot made it even easier,
letting me trick you in the most amusing way.
The revenge went exactly as planned.
I might have known
you're nothing but a bunch of fools!
Five centuries ago,
they got in my way,
and though I came close,
my incarnation failed.
Rather than admit defeat,
I selected you to be my next unwitting pawn.
A new sacrifice,
loved by mana,
still young,
and oh-so-easily swayed.
Tragedy,
a sense of purpose,
a mission to fulfill.
That's all it took
to turn you to forbidden magic
that would reincarnate the elves' souls
in human form.
No, you have it wrong.
Not me.
Licht was the one
who reincarnated us in human bodies.
It's true he delved into forbidden magic,
but he did it for us.
He gave us a chance.
You're incorrect.
Truth is,
he had nothing to do with your reincarnation.
Only, I'm afraid.
You don't understand
your leader's wishes.
He doesn't want
to exterminate humanity.
The restoration of the elves,
the revenge you so longed for,
false goals,
all of them.
You merely followed
the path that I laid for you
and led the other fools
along the way.
You did a truly splendid job.
I couldn't have asked
for a more useful tool,
and in the end,
it brought about
a future Licht
would never want.
and my incarnation,
allowing my soul
to return to my body
at last.
It's not true.
He's lying.
Well,
you were chosen,
that's true,
but not by the
four-leaf clover.
By me,
my little puppet.
Excellent work.
So amusing.
Elves and humans,
so alike.
Your dreams and ambitions
make the most excellent
playthings for creatures
like me.
when the owner of a four-leaf grimoire
is engulfed in deep despair,
a miracle happens.
A five-leaf grimoire
is born out of the darkness within.
At last,
I enjoy both my precious body
and my pitch-black grimoire.
Now I can rule this world,
a devil in possession
of my true form
and full power.
However,
we refuse to let
that devil win.
I spent all this time
in solitude
to prevent that
from happening.
Now that your seal
has finally been broken,
I'm assuming my own seal
will be released as well.
Huh?
Mero?
What a pathetic state
you're in.
If only my spell
had worked more completely.
No.
Without your help,
I couldn't return at all.
Huh?
It's good to see you again,
my prince.
At long last.
You're the first wizard king.
That statue,
it was you the whole time?
And how did Nero...
No way!
Nero, is that really you?
You look, um,
kind of different.
Today we will finally
put this conflict to rest.
And it's not just us two anymore.
We have friends now
who feel the way we do.
So please,
win this,
Asta.
I can feel this light
making me even stronger.
Looks like he's maxed out, though.
Sorry, Asta,
but if you can't keep up,
I'm ditching you.
You said no,
that's never going to happen!
That obnoxious fool
is merely letting himself
be pulled along
by his partner's spell.
They're no danger to me.
Where's the empty magic boy?
Hiding in the severed magic?
They're pulling each other in
with increasing speed!
Hiding in the severed magic!
What are you doing?
That's all I've got.
Now, what's up?
Nice try.
Mana Zone.
Dark Cloaked.
Dimension Slash.
Equinox!
Dark magic can interfere with the other world.
Curse that human!
I know that key, Captain.
Yanni.
I hate you!
Sealing recovery magic.
Heavenly prison.
Faint omen.
I've sealed his physical damage.
Now he just needs to draw out his anti-magic power.
Asta.
Die.
Derish.
Mishap!
You hurt!
You have to do nothing to try!
Asta?
Remember.
You're going to be the Wizard King!
Right here.
Right now!
I'm going to push past my limits!
Asta!
No!
IMPOSSIBLE!
It can't be!
I won't have it!
We've got a problem there, comrade.
Don't give me that.
Who are you?
Tell me!
You don't need to know that.
It doesn't matter how powerful you are.
You've lost this fight and you're about to disappear for good.
Farewell, you disgrace.
We... won!
I'm grateful.
We prevailed.
The time has come.
I don't have enough magic to hold this body together anymore.
My Prince...
Secre... or Nero, I suppose.
Will you watch their futures play out?
Watch them make the world better?
For my sake?
I've always been...
Well, um... I mean, anyway...
Let me go with you.
Please, sir.
I gave everything 500 years ago.
I should have died that day.
But then...
You help me protect the future.
Let me go.
Like I said, I can't let you seal off your potential.
I think the path ahead is a bright one.
Both for the magic knights and for the kingdom they'll fight to defend.
So do I. Really. Serving you for so long, it was an honor.
I was honored to have you, Secre.
Thank you for everything.
You did well.
Goodbye.
My Prince...
I'm sure there will be many more challenges for us to overcome.
But I know everything will be alright.
Because...
From now on...
I won't be alone.
Like...
Meet me.
Me.
Make it always.....
Maybe.
Meet me.
I think there are many black people.
I create an welcoming only one last step.
Then, if I have no longer one bird will come down.
One more time around....
We'll be right back.